Hi, my name is Victoria Wong, reporting for ABC-CC-CC-CC-7 News.
Today's feature will be taking a look at Downtown Naperville small businesses.
We interviewed local business owners and local residents to see what Downtown Naperville
could improve to enhance small businesses in the area around for visitors.
First, we interviewed Colin, the owner and manager of Purple Dog Records, a small shop
located on Washington Street that specializes in buying and selling used records, CDs, and
other music media.
Um, I was just better, better stores.
I mean, a lot of people were really disappointed when,
so when the Barnes and Noble moved from the main spot
in the middle of town to over on Jackson Avenue,
we thought like, oh, that's a big, you know,
that's a prime real estate right there.
And we were hoping that it was gonna be something cool,
something that was gonna bring people to downtown.
'Cause that's the old, where the Barnes and Noble used to be,
that was like a,
that's like a big location,
like right in the middle of the downtown area.
And so we were thinking like,
Oh, maybe if they, somebody put like a barcade there
or they put something like, you know,
just something, something cool, something, you know,
and, and then they put a bank and it was just like,
Oh, okay, cool.
Like, you know, at the very least it's like, you know,
like, like there could have been worse things
they could have put there.
They could have put like a data center
or something really, like really, really bad.
But at the same time, we were just like,
oh, well, you know, that's just a big location,
and it's just a bank now.
It's just kind of weird.
And so I just think that one thing that we could just use
just more, just better things in town,
like cooler stuff instead of just like,
like, as the town is filled,
mostly with like restaurants and bars,
which is great,
which is cool,
but it's just like,
you know,
like,
yeah,
we could use some other stuff as well.
Next,
we spoke with Jacob,
who's been the manager at Top Fashion for three years.
Downtown is a perfect one-stop shop for high-end streetwear staples.
located on Main Street.
Um, you know, I would say, you know, I feel like they've done a better job with the parking situation down here.
You know, we do have our own parking lot, but that's only, you know, like, five, six spaces that we have available.
You know, especially during the summer, it just gets really crowded down here.
You know, I think, you know, whether it's like community officers that are, you know,
tracking down people who are illegally parked, I think that helps.
Finally, we asked students from Naperville North what they believe can be improved about
the community in the downtown area.
I think we need a lot more parking as well as people parking.
more high school friendly activities other than just like shopping or buying clothing.
I think it really is just parking.
If we can find more places or have places that only workers can park, it'd be a lot
easier to get to my job as well as to find parking and be there on time.
I'd say more like open spaces maybe.
less like buildings being like put in like spots and more just like I'd say like more parks.
Well, that's a wrap on our feature. I'm Victoria Wong and thank you for tuning in.
And take this as a reminder, what can you improve on your community?